Intel® Ethernet Controller X710/XXV710/XL710 Adapters
Dynamic Device Personalization GTPv1 Package
============================================
December 10, 2018

Contents
========
Overview
Limitations and Prerequisites
Legal / Disclaimers


Overview
========
This package contains all the required files to update the parser on the
Intel® Ethernet Controller X710/XXV710/XL710 adapters in your system.
It contains the binary package file .pkg and checksum file for .pkg file.
MPLS connects with the existing router, and the MPLS profile can inspect the tunnel header so that
traffic can be directed into multiple queues, which can later be processed by multiple cores.

Limitations and Prerequisites
=============================
This package should only be used on Intel® Ethernet Controller X710/XXV710/XL710
branded adapters starting with firmware 6.01.
Please contact your OEM vendor for an appropriate package.

DO NOT
- Power down your system during downloading package to an adapter.
- Remove the NIC before the package downloading completes.
- Interrupt the package downloading to an adapter in any other way.
Doing so may make your device unusable and will require device reset.


Legal / Disclaimers
===================
Copyright (C) 2018, Intel Corporation. All rights reserved.

Intel Corporation assumes no responsibility for errors or omissions in this
document. Nor does Intel make any commitment to update the information
contained herein.

Intel is a trademark of Intel Corporation in the U.S. and/or other countries.

*Other names and brands may be claimed as the property of others.

This software is furnished under license and may only be used or copied
in accordance with the terms of the license. The information in this
manual is furnished for informational use only, is subject to change
without notice, and should not be construed as a commitment by Intel
Corporation. Intel Corporation assumes no responsibility or liability
for any errors or inaccuracies that may appear in this document or any
software that may be provided in association with this document. Except
as permitted by such license, no part of this document may be reproduced,
stored in a retrieval system, or transmitted in any form or by any means
without the express written consent of Intel Corporation.
